{
    "subject": "resource/Bruce_Willis",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Idar-Oberstein",
    "human_readable": "Bruce Willis was born in Idar-Oberstein.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8105794191360474,
            "question": "Where was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7933054566383362,
            "question": "In what country was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7781732678413391,
            "question": "Name the city where Bruce Willis was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7659872174263,
            "question": "When was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45147064328193665,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32282012701034546,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2353184074163437,
            "question": "Which films has Bruce Willis starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1992628425359726,
            "question": "Is Bruce Willis involved in any other creative fields besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17003943026065826,
            "question": "Has Bruce Willis won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15225130319595337,
            "question": "What genre of film is Bruce Willis most associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bruce Willis was born in Idar-Oberstein.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7832_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Bruce Willis won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7832_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bruce Willis involved in any other creative fields besides acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7832_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which films has Bruce Willis starred in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7832_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7832_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provide multiple confirmations of Bruce Willis's birthplace as Idar-Oberstein, West Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Bruce Willis being born in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany. For example:\n\n- From `45.txt`: \"Bruce Willis was born on March 19, 1955, in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany.\"\n- From `70.txt`: \"Hollywood star Bruce Willis strayed off the typical German tourist track this weekend to visit the place of his birth in the town of Idar-Oberstein.\"\n- From `32.txt`: \"Walter Bruce Willis was born on March 19, 1955, in Idar-Oberstein, West Germany, to a German mother, Marlene Kassel, and an American father, David Andrew Willis (from Carneys Point, New Jersey), who were then living on a United States military base.\"\n- From `15.txt`: \"Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955, Idar-Oberstein, West Germany), known professionally as Bruce Willis...\"\n\nThese statements collectively support the statement that Bruce Willis was born in Idar-Oberstein."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}